Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 5, Section 1: Boxes 1-22 1870-2017
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 5, Section 1: Boxes 1-22
- Association of American Railroads, Publication (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Item 11: The Facts About Competitive Access, Publication (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Item 12: What Are The Railroads Doing About Alcohol and Drug Abuse, Publication (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Item 13: Storms, disasters Bring Railroads to the Rescue, Publication (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Item 14: College Professors of Subjects Relating to transportation, Publication (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Item 15: When It Comes to Fuel-Efficiency. Railroads Lead the Transportation Pack, Publication (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Item 16: The Saga of the Vanishing Caboose, Publication (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Item 17: Mergers -- Efficiency's the Target, Publication (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Item 18: high Technology Rides the Rails, Publication (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Item 19: Profiles of Class I Railroads, Publication (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Item 20: America's Railroads After Staggers: And Economic Prospectus, Publication (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Item 21: Railroad Facts, Publication (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Item 22: Railroads and the Marketplace, Publication (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Item 23: A Step-By-Step Process, Publication (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Item 24: The Impact of a Railroad Strike, Publication (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Item 25: Alcohol and Drug Abuse: America Can't Afford it, And Neither Can Its Railroads, Publication (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Item 26: Alcohol and Drug Abuse: America Can't Afford It, and neither Can Its Railroads, Publication (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Item 27: In America's Diverse Railroad Industry One Thing Is Universal: A Commitment to Safety, Publication (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Item 28: High-Tech Railroading: Highballing Into The Future, Publication (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Item 29: General Information, Publication (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Association of American Railroads, Publication (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Item 2: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 13)
    May 9. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 13)
    May 23. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 13)
    June 6. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Item 6: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 13)
    July 4. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 13)
    July 18. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 13)
    August 1. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Item 10: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 13)
    Aug 15. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Item 12: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 13)
    Aug 29. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 13)
    Sept 12. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 13)
    Oct 24. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 13)
    Sept 26. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 13)
    Oct 10. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 13)
    Nov 21. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 13)
    Nov 7. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 13)
    Dec 5. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 13)
    Dec 19. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 13)
    Jan 23. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 13)
    Feb 6. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 13)
    Mar 6. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 13)
    Mar 20. Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 13)
    April 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 13)
    May 1. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 13)
    April 18. Item is in English.
  - Item 28: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 13)
    May 15. Item is in English.
  - Item 29: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 13)
    May 29. Item is in English.
  - Item 30: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 13)
    Jun 12. Item is in English.
  - Item 31: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 13)
    Jun 26. Item is in English.
  - Item 32: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 13)
    Jul 10. Item is in English.
  - Item 33: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 13)
    Jul 25. Item is in English.
  - Item 34: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 13)
    Aug 7. Item is in English.
  - Item 35: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 13)
    Sept 4. Item is in English.
  - Item 36: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 13)
    Aug 21. Item is in English.
  - Item 37: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 13)
    Sept 18. Item is in English.
  - Item 38: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 13)
    Oct 2. Item is in English.
- Association of American Railroads, Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: On excel spreadsheet, Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Item 2: On Track, Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
    By Association of American Railroads. v.3:no.3 (1989:February). Item is in English.
  - Item 3: On Track, Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
    By Association of American Railroads. v.3:no.4 (1989:February). Item is in English.
  - Item 4: On Track, Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
    By Association of American Railroads. v.3:no.5 (1989:March). Item is in English.
  - Item 5: On Track, Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
    By Association of American Railroads. v.3:no.6 (1989:March). Item is in English.
  - Item 6: On Track, Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
    By Association of American Railroads. v.3:no.7 (1989:April). Item is in English.
  - Item 7: On Track, Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
    By Association of American Railroads. v.3:no.8 (1989:April). Item is in English.
  - Item 8: On Track, Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
    By Association of American Railroads. v.3:no.9 (1989:May). Item is in English.
  - Item 9: On Track, Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
    By Association of American Railroads. v.3:no.10 (1989:May). Item is in English.
  - Item 10: On Track, Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
    By Association of American Railroads. v.3:no.11 (1989:June). Item is in English.
  - Item 11: On Track, Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
    By Association of American Railroads. v.3:no.12 (1989:June). Item is in English.
  - Item 12: On Track, Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
    By Association of American Railroads. v.3:no.13 (1989:July). Item is in English.
  - Item 13: On Track, Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
    By Association of American Railroads. v.3:no.14 (1989:July). Item is in English.
  - Item 14: On Track, Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
    By Association of American Railroads. v.3:no.15 (1989:August). Item is in English.
  - Item 15: On Track, Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
    By Association of American Railroads. v.3:no.16 (1989:August). Item is in English.
  - Item 16: On Track, Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
    By Association of American Railroads. v.3:no.17 (1989:September). Item is in English.
  - Item 17: On Track, Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
    By Association of American Railroads. v.3:no.18 (1989:September). Item is in English.
  - Item 18: On Track, Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
    By Association of American Railroads. v.3:no.19 (1989:October). Item is in English.
  - Item 19: On Track, Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
    By Association of American Railroads. v.3:no.20 (1989:November). Item is in English.
  - Item 20: On Track, Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
    By Association of American Railroads. v.3:no.21 (1989:November). Item is in English.
  - Item 21: On Track, Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
    By Association of American Railroads. v.3:no.22 (1989:November). Item is in English.
  - Item 22: On Track, Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
    By Association of American Railroads. v.3:no.23 (1989:December). Item is in English.
  - Item 23: On Track, Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
    By Association of American Railroads. v.4:no.1 (1990:January). Item is in English.
  - Item 24: On Track, Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
    By Association of American Railroads. v.4:no.2 (1990:January). Item is in English.
  - Item 25: On Track, Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
    By Association of American Railroads. v.4:no.4 (1990:February). Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Rail News Update Subcription Notification, Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
    By Association of American Railroads. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
    By Association of American Railroads. no.2517 (1989:February 15). Item is in English.
  - Item 28: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
    By Association of American Railroads. no.2518 (1989:March 1). Item is in English.
  - Item 29: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
    By Association of American Railroads. no.2519 (1989:March 15). Item is in English.
  - Item 30: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
    By Association of American Railroads. no.2520 (1989:March 29). Item is in English.
  - Item 31: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
    By Association of American Railroads. no.2521 (1989:April 12). Item is in English.
  - Item 32: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
    By Association of American Railroads. no.2522 (1989:April 26). Item is in English.
  - Item 33: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
    By Association of American Railroads. no.2523 (1989:May 10). Item is in English.
  - Item 34: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
    By Association of American Railroads. no.2523 (1989:May 24). Item is in English.
  - Item 35: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
    By Association of American Railroads. no.2524 (1989:June 7). Item is in English.
  - Item 36: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
    By Association of American Railroads. no.2525 (1989:June 21). Item is in English.
  - Item 37: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
    By Association of American Railroads. no.2526 (1989:July 5). Item is in English.
  - Item 38: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
    By Association of American Railroads. no.2527 (1989:July 19). Item is in English.
  - Item 39: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
    By Association of American Railroads. no.2528 (1989:August 2). Item is in English.
  - Item 40: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
    By Association of American Railroads. no.2528 (1989:August 2). Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 41: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
    By Association of American Railroads. no.2527 (1989:August 16). Item is in English.
  - Item 42: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
    By Association of American Railroads. no.2528 (1989:August 30). Item is in English.
  - Item 43: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
    By Association of American Railroads. no.2529 (1989:September 13). Item is in English.
  - Item 44: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
    By Association of American Railroads. no.2529 (1989:September 13). Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 45: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
    By Association of American Railroads. no.2532 (1989:September 27). Item is in English.
  - Item 46: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
    By Association of American Railroads. no.2533 (1989:October 11). Item is in English.
  - Item 47: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
    By Association of American Railroads. no.2534 (1989:October 25). Item is in English.
  - Item 48: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
    By Association of American Railroads. no.2535 (1989:November 8). Item is in English.
  - Item 49: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
    By Association of American Railroads. no.2536 (1989:November 22). Item is in English.
  - Item 50: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
    By Association of American Railroads. no.2537 (1989:December 6). Item is in English.
  - Item 51: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
    By Association of American Railroads. no.2539 (1990:January 3). Item is in English.
  - Item 52: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
    By Association of American Railroads. no.2540 (1990:January 17). Item is in English.
  - Item 53: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
    By Association of American Railroads. no.2541 (1990:January 31). Item is in English.
  - Item 54: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
    By Association of American Railroads. no.2542 (1990:February 14). Item is in English.
  - Item 55: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
    By Association of American Railroads. no.2543 (1990:February 28). Item is in English.
  - Item 56: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
    By Association of American Railroads. no.2544 (1990:March 14). Item is in English.
  - Item 57: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
    By Association of American Railroads. no.2545 (1990:March 28). Item is in English.
  - Item 58: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
    By Association of American Railroads. no.2546 (1990:April 11). Item is in English.
- Association of American Railroads, Publication (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: On Track, Publication (Box 5, Folder 15)
    By Association of American Railroads. v.2:no.7 (1988:April). Item is in English.
  - Item 2: On Track, Publication (Box 5, Folder 15)
    By Association of American Railroads. v.2:no.8 (1988:April). Item is in English.
  - Item 3: On Track, Publication (Box 5, Folder 15)
    By Association of American Railroads. v.2:no.9 (1988:May). Item is in English.
  - Item 4: On Track, Publication (Box 5, Folder 15)
    By Association of American Railroads. v.2:no.10 (1988:May). Item is in English.
  - Item 5: On Track, Publication (Box 5, Folder 15)
    By Association of American Railroads. v.2:no.11 (1988:June). Item is in English.
  - Item 6: On Track, Publication (Box 5, Folder 15)
    By Association of American Railroads. v.2:no.12 (1988:June). Item is in English.
  - Item 7: On Track, Publication (Box 5, Folder 15)
    By Association of American Railroads. v.2:no.13 (1988:July). Item is in English.
  - Item 8: On Track, Publication (Box 5, Folder 15)
    By Association of American Railroads. v.2:no.14 (1988:July). Item is in English.
  - Item 9: On Track, Publication (Box 5, Folder 15)
    By Association of American Railroads. v.2:no.15 (1988:August). Item is in English.
  - Item 10: On Track, Publication (Box 5, Folder 15)
    By Association of American Railroads. v.2:no.16 (1988:August). Item is in English.
  - Item 11: On Track, Publication (Box 5, Folder 15)
    By Association of American Railroads. v.2:no.17 (1988:September). Item is in English.
  - Item 12: On Track, Publication (Box 5, Folder 15)
    By Association of American Railroads. v.2:no.18 (1988:September). Item is in English.
  - Item 13: On Track, Publication (Box 5, Folder 15)
    By Association of American Railroads. v.2:no.19 (1988:October). Item is in English.
  - Item 14: On Track, Publication (Box 5, Folder 15)
    By Association of American Railroads. v.2:no.20 (1988:October). Item is in English.
  - Item 15: On Track, Publication (Box 5, Folder 15)
    By Association of American Railroads. v.2:no.21 (1988:November). Item is in English.
  - Item 16: On Track, Publication (Box 5, Folder 15)
    By Association of American Railroads. v.2:no.22 (1988:November). Item is in English.
  - Item 17: On Track, Publication (Box 5, Folder 15)
    By Association of American Railroads. v.2:no.23 (1988:December). Item is in English.
  - Item 18: On Track, Publication (Box 5, Folder 15)
    By Association of American Railroads. v.3:no.1 (1989:January). Item is in English.
  - Item 19: On Track, Publication (Box 5, Folder 15)
    By Association of American Railroads. v.3:no.2 (1989:January). Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 15)
    By Association of American Railroads. no.2495 (1988:April 13). Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 15)
    By Association of American Railroads. no.2496 (1988:April 27). Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 15)
    By Association of American Railroads. no.2496 (1988:April 27). Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 15)
    By Association of American Railroads. no.2497 (1988:May 11). Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 15)
    By Association of American Railroads. no.2497 (1988:May 11). Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 15)
    By Association of American Railroads. no.2498 (1988:May 25). Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 15)
    By Association of American Railroads. no.2498 (1988:May 25). Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 15)
    By Association of American Railroads. no.2499 (1988:June 8). Item is in English.
  - Item 28: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 15)
    By Association of American Railroads. no.2499 (1988:June 8). Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 29: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 15)
    By Association of American Railroads. no.2500 (1988:June 22). Item is in English.
  - Item 30: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 15)
    By Association of American Railroads. no.2500 (1988:June 22). Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 31: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 15)
    By Association of American Railroads. no.2501 (1988:July 6). Item is in English.
  - Item 32: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 15)
    By Association of American Railroads. no.2501 (1988:July 6). Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 33: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 15)
    By Association of American Railroads. no.2502 (1988:July 20). Item is in English.
  - Item 34: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 15)
    By Association of American Railroads. no.2502 (1988:July 20). Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 35: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 15)
    By Association of American Railroads. no.2503 (1988:August 3). Item is in English.
  - Item 36: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 15)
    By Association of American Railroads. no.2503 (1988:August 3). Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 37: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 15)
    By Association of American Railroads. no.2504 (1988:August 17). Item is in English.
  - Item 38: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 15)
    By Association of American Railroads. no.2504 (1988:August 17). Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 39: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 15)
    By Association of American Railroads. no.2505 (1988:August 31). Item is in English.
  - Item 40: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 15)
    By Association of American Railroads. no.2505 (1988:August 31). Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 41: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 15)
    By Association of American Railroads. no.2506 (1988:September 14). Item is in English.
  - Item 42: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 15)
    By Association of American Railroads. no.2506 (1988:September 14). Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 43: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 15)
    By Association of American Railroads. no.2507 (1988:September 28). Item is in English.
  - Item 44: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 15)
    By Association of American Railroads. no.2507 (1988:September 28). Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 45: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 15)
    By Association of American Railroads. no.2508 (1988:October 12). Item is in English.
  - Item 46: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 15)
    By Association of American Railroads. no.2508 (1988:October 12). Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 47: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 15)
    By Association of American Railroads. no.2509 (1988:October 26). Item is in English.
  - Item 48: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 15)
    By Association of American Railroads. no.2509 (1988:October 26). Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 49: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 15)
    By Association of American Railroads. no.2510 (1988:November 9). Item is in English.
  - Item 50: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 15)
    By Association of American Railroads. no.2511 (1988:November 23). Item is in English.
  - Item 51: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 15)
    By Association of American Railroads. no.2512 (1988:December 7). Item is in English.
  - Item 52: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 15)
    By Association of American Railroads. no.2513 (1988:December 21). Item is in English.
  - Item 53: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 15)
    By Association of American Railroads. no.2514 (1989:January 4). Item is in English.
  - Item 54: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 15)
    By Association of American Railroads. no.2515 (1989:January 18). Item is in English.
  - Item 55: Rail News Update, Publication (Box 5, Folder 15)
    By Association of American Railroads. no.2516 (1989:January 1). Item is in English.
  - Item 56: College Professors of Subjects Related to Transportation, Publication (Box 5, Folder 15)
    By Association of American Railroads. August 23, 1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 57: Background: Coal and the Railroads, Publication (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Item 58: Background: Improved U.S. Grain Exports, Publication (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Association of American Railroads, Publication (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: On Track, Publication (Box 5, Folder 16)
    By Association of American Railroads. v.1:no.1 (1987:February). Item is in English.
  - Item 2: On Track, Publication (Box 5, Folder 16)
    By Association of American Railroads. v.1:no.8 (1987:May). Item is in English.
  - Item 3: On Track, Publication (Box 5, Folder 16)
    By Association of American Railroads. v.1:no.9 (1987:June). Item is in English.
  - Item 4: On Track, Publication (Box 5, Folder 16)
    By Association of American Railroads. v.1:no.10 (1987:June). Item is in English.
  - Item 5: On Track, Publication (Box 5, Folder 16)
    By Association of American Railroads. v.1:no.11 (1987:July). Item is in English.
  - Item 6: On Track, Publication (Box 5, Folder 16)
    By Association of American Railroads. v.1:no.12 (1987:July). Item is in English.
  - Item 7: On Track, Publication (Box 5, Folder 16)
    By Association of American Railroads. v.1:no.13 (1987:August). Item is in English.
  - Item 8: On Track, Publication (Box 5, Folder 16)
    By Association of American Railroads. v.1:no.14 (1987:August). Item is in English.
  - Item 9: On Track, Publication (Box 5, Folder 16)
    By Association of American Railroads. v.1:no.15 (1987:September). Item is in English.
  - Item 10: On Track, Publication (Box 5, Folder 16)
    By Association of American Railroads. v.1:no.16 (1987:September). Item is in English.